<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Frum Jerusalem</string>

    <!-- Category name for restaurants [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_restaurants">Dining</string>

    <!-- Category name for parks [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_parks">Parks</string>

    <!-- Category name for religious sites [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_indoors">Indoors</string>

    <!-- Category name for attractions [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_outdoors">Outdoors</string>

    <!-- Place holder strings -->
    <string name="location_placeHolder">The Kotel</string>
    <string name="opening_hours_placeHolder">Open 24 hours</string>
    <string name="description_placeHolder">This is a short description</string>

    <!-- Clickable Views in Details Activity -->
    <string name="directions">Directions</string>
    <string name="call">Call</string>
    <string name="website">Website</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>

    <string name="noPhoneNumber">No phone Number</string>

    <!-- The Kotel -->
    <string name="kotel_name">The Kotel</string>
    <string name="kotel_summary">Last remaining wall of Second Temple. Holy Jewish site</string>
    <string name="kotel_times">Open 24 Hours</string>
    <string name="kotel_description">The Western Wall or Kotel, is an ancient limestone wall in the Old City of Jerusalem.\n
        It is a relatively small segment of a far longer ancient retaining wall.
        The wall was originally erected as part of the expansion of the Second Jewish Temple begun by Herod the Great.
        The Western Wall is considered holy due to its connection to the Temple Mount</string>
    <string name="kotel_address">The Old City</string>
    <string name="kotel_url">https://english.thekotel.org/</string>
    <string name="kotel_phone_number">+972&#8211;26271333</string>

    <!-- Machane Yehudah -->
    <string name="machane_yehudah_name">Machane Yehudah</string>
    <string name="machane_yehudah_summary">Vibrant Market In Central Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="machane_yehudah_times">8am until 7pm</string>
    <string name="machane_yehudah_description">World-famous icons of Jerusalem include the Western Wall, the Tower of David and the Machane Yehuda market.
        The Western Wall and the Tower of David represent the religious, historical nature of Jerusalem, the place from which the Jewish people developed.
        Machane Yehuda market, however, represents the contemporary—and the future heart of Jerusalem.
        Machane Yehuda integrates, in a unique way, the old and the new. Both a bustling marketplace and a neighborhood, it incorporates food, drink, shopping, bars, restaurants.
        The shuk still retains its most important characteristics, it remains authentic, with all the flavors and aromas, the colors and the traders interaction with the crowds.
        The Machane Yehuda market is widely recognized as a symbol of the Jerusalem, and for a very good reason: Jerusalemites see it as a place that represents them, symbolizes them,
        and gives them a unique identity in a larger Israeli social context. But this name has something inexpressible to language.Even though Jerusalem today has many shopping and entertainment centers,
        some are even at several hotels in Jerusalem, there is something about the Machane Yehuda market that attracts people, even without a shopping list. Perhaps it is the ability to simply be who we are people who love life and who love Jerusalem.</string>
    <string name="machane_yehudah_address">Rehov Mahane Yehuda, Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="machane_yehuah_url">http://en.machne.co.il/</string>

    <!-- Biblical Zoo -->
    <string name="zoo_name">The Biblical Zoo</string>
    <string name="zoo_summary">The Biggest Zoo In Israel</string>
    <string name="zoo_times">9am until 6pm</string>
    <string name="zoo_description">The Tisch Family Zoological Gardens, also known as the Biblical Zoo, opened in Jerusalem’s Malha neighborhood in 1993.
        The Zoo Stretches across almost 100 acres, and is ranked year after year as one of the top tourist sites in Israel, attracting over 750,000 visitors annually.
        The Zoo’s scenic location in the Judean hills with its varied animal exhibits, draws people from all threads of Jerusalem’s vibrant social fabric Jewish,
        Christian and Muslim; secular and religious: young and old; and tourists and locals. Thus the Zoo has become a bridge between communities.
        It is one of the few sites in Israel where everyone comes together and feels welcome.</string>
    <string name="zoo_address">1 Derech Aharon Shulov, Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="zoo_url">http://www.jerusalemzoo.org/</string>
    <string name="zoo_phone_number">+972&#8211;26750111</string>

    <!-- Yemin Moshe -->
    <string name="yemin_name">Yemin Moshe</string>
    <string name="yemin_summary">First neighborhood outside old city walls</string>
    <string name="yemin_times">Open 24 hours</string>
    <string name="yemin_description">Yemin Moshe was established in 1892–1894 by the Montefiore Welfare Fund.
        Located outside Jerusalem\'s Old City, it was conceived as a solution to the overcrowding and unsanitary
        conditions inside the walls. The Fund was continuing the work done by British Jewish banker Moses Montefiore
        and the new project was meant to mark the seventh year after the philanthropist's death.
        The name commemorates Montefiore's first name and a verse from the Book of Isaiah.</string>
    <string name="yemin_address">Yemin Moshe, Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="yemin_url">https://www.touristisrael.com/yemin-moshe-jerusalem/6111/</string>

    <!-- Jaffa Gate -->
    <string name="jaffa_name">Jaffa Gate</string>
    <string name="jaffa_times">Open 24 Hours</string>
    <string name="jaffa_summary">Main entrance into the Ol City</string>
    <string name="jaffa_description">One of the seven open gates of the Old City, Jaffa Gate serves as the main tourist
        entry point to the city. Just inside the gate, you’ll find the Old City bazaar and the Tower of David Museum.
        Jaffa Gate is one of the most beautiful and important gates among the gates of the Ottoman city wall from the 16th century.
        The gate is named after Jaffa- the city to which this path lead. The Arab name for this gate is “Bab El Khalil”,
        named after the city of Hebron (El Khalil in Arabic) to which the southern path starting from Jaffa Gate leads.</string>
    <string name="jaffa_address">Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="jaffa_url">https://www.itraveljerusalem.com/ent/jaffa-gate/</string>



    <!-- The Israel Museum -->
    <string name="israel_museum_name">The Israel Museum</string>
    <string name="israel_museum_summary">Amazing historical artifacts of The People of Israel</string>
    <string name="israel_museum_times">10am until 5pm</string>
    <string name="israel_museum_description">The Israel Museum  was established in 1965 as Israel\'s national museum.
        Among the unique objects on display are the Venus of Berekhat Ram, the interior of a 1736 Zedek ve Shalom synagogue from Suriname,
        necklaces worn by Jewish brides in Yemen and a mosaic Islamic prayer niche from 17th-century Persia.
        An urn-shaped building on the grounds of the museum, the Shrine of the Book,
        houses the Dead Sea Scrolls and artifacts discovered at Masada. It is one of the largest museums in the region.</string>
    <string name="israel_museum_address">Derech Ruppin 11</string>
    <string name="israel_museum_url">http://www.imj.org.il/en/</string>
    <string name="israel_museum_phone_number">+9722&#8211;6708811</string>

    <!-- Yad Vashem -->
    <string name="yad_vashem_name">Yad Vashem</string>
    <string name="yad_vashem_summary">Holocaust Memorial Center</string>
    <string name="yad_vashem_times">8:30am until 5pm</string>
    <string name="yad_vashem_decription">Yad Vashem is Israel\'s official memorial to the victims of the Holocaust.
        It is dedicated to preserving the memory of the dead; honoring Jews who fought against their Nazi oppressors and Gentiles
        who selflessly aided Jews in need, and researching the phenomenon of the Holocaust in particular and genocide in general,
        with the aim of avoiding such events in the future.</string>
    <string name="yad_vashem_address">Har Hazikaron, Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="yad_vashem_url">https://www.yadvashem.org/</string>
    <string name="yad_vashem_phone_number">+9722&#8211;6443400</string>

    <!-- The Israel Aquarium -->
    <string name="aquarium_name">The Israel Aquarium</string>
    <string name="aquarium_summary">Israel\'s first and only Aquarium!</string>
    <string name="aquarium_times">Advance Bookings Only</string>
    <string name="aquarium_description">The Gottesman Family Israel Aquarium, Jerusalem is a public aquarium in Israel inaugurated
        on 19.6.2017. The aquarium focuses on Israel\'s marine environment - the Red Sea and the Mediterranean Sea as well
        as on the Sea of Galilee and the Dead Sea. The aquarium was built by the Tish Family Zoological Gardens
        (the Biblical Zoo in Jerusalem) and is located next to it, but stands on its own as a separate tourist attraction.
        The aquarium will open to the general public for a running in period during the summer of 2017. </string>
    <string name="aquarium_address">1 Aharon Shulov, Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="aquarium_url">https://www.israel-aquarium.org.il/english</string>
    <string name="aquarium_phone_number">+97273&#8211;3399000</string>

    <!-- Science Museum -->
    <string name="science_museum_name">Bloomfield Science Museum</string>
    <string name="science_museum_summary">A fun packed educational day out</string>
    <string name="science_museum_times">10am until 6pm</string>
    <string name="science_museum_description">The Bloomfield Science Museum in Jerusalem is an informal cultural and educational institution
        that presents exhibitions consisting of interactive exhibits on subjects of science and technology,
        and integrates these exhibits into a context through a wide range of educational activities.
        The goals of the museum are to increase interest among the general public in science and technology
        in the world around us, to promote excellency in sciences among youth, and to present science and technology
        as an integral part of human culture.</string>
    <string name="science_museum_address">Museum Boulevard, Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="science_museum_url">http://www.mada.org.il/en/</string>
    <string name="science_museum_phone_number">+9722&#8211;6544888</string>

    <!-- Kotel Tunnel Tours -->
    <string name="tunnel_tours_name">Kotel Tunnel Tours</string>
    <string name="tunnel_tours_summary">A journey through time to the history of Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="tunnel_tours_times">7am until late at night</string>
    <string name="tunnel_tours_description">The Western Wall of the Temple Mount is one of the most magnificent
        and significant remnants in Jerusalem from the days of the Second Temple, destroyed approximately 2,000 years ago.
        The Western Wall stretches along almost half a kilometer, but today, the part visible to all at the Western Wall Plaza
        is a mere 70 meters of it. The tour of the Western Wall Tunnels allows visitors to reach the segments of the Wall hidden
        from view, and to touch the original and special stones that tell the story of the Jewish nation. Visitors to the Western
        Wall Tunnels walk through ancient and fascinating subterranean spaces with exquisite archeological findings, such as large
        stone arches, water pits, an ancient water aqueduct that ends at the Strouthion Pool, and more.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_tours_address">Entrance from the Kotel</string>
    <string name="tunnel_tours_url">https://english.thekotel.org/western_wall_sites/western_wall_tunnels/</string>
    <string name="tunnel_tours_phone_number">+9722&#8211;6271333</string>

    <!-- Teddy Park -->
    <string name="teddy_park_name">Teddy Park</string>
    <string name="teddy_park_summary">Have fun in the fountains</string>
    <string name="teddy_park_times">7am until 10pp</string>
    <string name="teddy_park_description">Teddy Park is a public park situated opposite Jerusalem\'s Old City and David\'s Citadel.
        The park was developed by the Jerusalem Foundation in memory of Jerusalem\'s long serving mayor, Teddy Kollek
        and opened to the public in 2013. A major feature of the park is its splash fountain that orchestrates animated water,
        sound and lighting. Water shoots from the fountains in sync with music every 30 minutes.
        In the evening a light show plays while during the day children run among the water spouts.</string>
    <string name="teddy_park_address">Pele Yoets Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="teddy_park_url">https://www.funinjerusalem.com/teddy-kollek-park/</string>

    <!-- Gan Hapaamon -->
    <string name="bell_park_name">Gan HaPaamon</string>
    <string name="bell_park_summary">Park with activities for children</string>
    <string name="bell_park_times">Open 24 hours</string>
    <string name="bell_park_description">Gan HaPaamon, also known as Liberty Bell Park, is located in the center of Jerusalem.
        The park boasts playgrounds, a skating rink, a children’s theatre, and lots of shady lawns.
        Gan HaPa’amon is named for the miniature liberty bell at the entrance to the park.
        The bell, a miniature of Philadelphia’s liberty bell, was added to the park in honor of the United States
        centennial celebrations in 1976. The bell was a gift from the city of Philadelphia.</string>
    <string name="bell_park_address">Intersection of Keren Hayesod and King David Street, Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="bell_park_url">https://www.triphobo.com/places/jerusalem-israel/liberty-bell-park</string>

    <!-- The Rose Garden -->
    <string name="rose_garden_name">The Wohl Rose Garden</string>
    <string name="rose_garden_summary">A wonderful place to relax</string>
    <string name="rode_garden_times">7am untl 10pm</string>
    <string name="rose_garden_description">Wohl Rose Garden is a public garden in Givat Ram, Jerusalem, located opposite
        the Knesset and government precinct, at the foot of the Israeli Supreme Court. Over 400 varieties of roses are grown there,
        many of them gifts from countries around the world. It is one of the few rose parks of its kind in the Middle East,
        where there is no rainfall in summer. The park\'s Garden of Nations is made up of sections donated by other countries.
        Each section has rose varieties characteristic of, or grown in, the respective country.
        The park also has an experimental section where new varieties of roses are tested for their suitability for
        public and private gardens in Israel </string>
    <string name="rose_garden_address">Eliezer Kaplan Street Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="rose_garden_url">https://www.tripadvisor.com/Attraction_Review-g293983-d558590-Reviews-Wohl_Rose_Garden-Jerusalem_Jerusalem_District.html</string>

    <!-- The Botanical Gardens -->
    <string name="bot_gardens_name">The Botanical Gardens</string>
    <string name="bot_gardens_summary">For the flower lovers</string>
    <string name="bot_gardens_times">9am untl 7pm</string>
    <string name="bot_gardens_description">The Jerusalem Botanical Gardens is a gem in the heart of Jerusalem.
        It serves as an education, learning and research center, holds a diverse collection of plants from around the world
        which are displayed geographically and is a destination for tourism, recreation and cultural events.
        At around 30 acres, the Jerusalem Botanical Gardens is the largest in Israel.
        There are over 6,000 species and varieties of plants from around the world – Israel’s largest collection of live plants
         displayed in 6 phyto-geographical sections – Southern Africa, Europe, North America, Australia, South-East
        and Central Asia and the Mediterranean. The sections simulate the landscapes of these areas and so there is always
        something blooming at the Jerusalem Botanical Gardens.</string>
    <string name="bot_gardens_address">Zalman Shneur Street 1, Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="bot_gardens_url">https://www.botanic.co.il/en/</string>
    <string name="bot_gardens_phone_number">+9722&#8211;6794012</string>

    <!-- Gan Sachar-->
    <string name="gan_sachar_name">Gan Sachar</string>
    <string name="gan_sachar_summary">A great place for a picnic</string>
    <string name="gan_sachar_times">Open 24 Hours</string>
    <string name="gan_sachar_description">The first thing one notices when presented with the expanse of west
        Jerusalem\'s Gan Sacher (Sacher Park) is a simple plant common in much of the world but rare
        in the big cities and towns of Israel: grass. Jerusalem, for all its venerable charm,
        is not a particularly verdant city, with only its parks offering any large amount of green space.
        But the parks are impressive, and Gan Sacher is the best of the lot, a kilometers-long stretch of
        space separating Nachlaot and Rechavia from the government complex housing the Knesset and the Supreme Court.</string>
    <string name="gan_sachar_address">Ben Zvi Boulevard</string>
    <string name="gan_sachar_url">https://www.tripadvisor.com/Attraction_Review-g293983-d8460341-Reviews-Gan_Sacher_Park-Jerusalem_Jerusalem_District.html</string>

    <!-- Entrecote -->
    <string name="entrecote_name">Entrecote</string>
    <string name="entrecote_summary">A fine Fleshig Restaurant</string>
    <string name="entrecote_times">12pm unitl 12am</string>
    <string name="entrecote_description">The focus at Entrecote is on meat – prepared on the grill or in a taboon (brick oven).
        Entrecote is located in Har Hotzvim and enjoys beautiful views. The menu offers diners a Kosher le-Mehadrin meat menu
        (Glatt Kosher - Rabbi Mahfoud). The courteous waiting staff provide friendly, professional service. Entrecote got its
        name because of the restaurant\'s flagship dish – premium, juicy entrecote steaks aged for several weeks at an unchanging
        temperature and then spiced with a special spice mixture created by the chef and owner, Dudu Asraf. Our terrific steaks
        are served in five weights - 300, 500, 700 and 900 grams.</string>
    <string name="entrecote_address">1 Hamarpeh Street, Har Hotzvim</string>
    <string name="entrecote_url">http://www.entrecote.rest-e.co.il/</string>
    <string name="entrecote_phone_number">+972539443066</string>

    <!-- Skyline -->
    <string name="skyline_name">Skyline Restaurant</string>
    <string name="skyline_summary">A restaurant with a view</string>
    <string name="skyline_times">12pm until 12am</string>
    <string name="skyline_description">Skyline Chef is one of the most unique restaurants in all of Jerusalem.
        The breathtaking panoramic views of the city from the roof top of the Jerusalem Gardens Hotel and Spa make dining
        a memorable experience. The restaurant provides an intimate setting for both indoor and outdoor dining.All foods from
        the breads and dips to the desserts are made on the premises thus providing the freshest possible taste experience.
        The menus are seasonal and focus is given to the daily specials.
        The highest standards of kashrut are adhered to and Skyline Chef is strictly OU Glatt Mehadrin and
        Rabbanut Mehadrin and uses Rubin meat.</string>
    <string name="skyline_address">4 Zeev Vilnai Sreett Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="skyline_url">http://www.skylinejerusalem.com/</string>
    <string name="skyline_phone_number">+9722&#8211;6558847</string>

    <!-- Sheyan -->
    <string name="sheyan_name">Sheyan Asian Restaurant</string>
    <string name="sheyan_summary">Jerusalem\'s finest asian restaurant</string>
    <string name="sheyan_times">12pm until 3pm and 6pm until 11pm</string>
    <string name="sheyan_description">Sheyan is a Chinese/Asian restaurant situated in the historic windmill in Jerusalem\'s Rehavia
        neighborhood. The kosher restaurant (whose name means “the last rays of sunset” and is also the name of the city where
        the first restaurant in China was opened), offers a successful fusion of traditional Chinese cuisine with Jerusalem\'s
        one-of-a-kind atmosphere. Its menu features kosher dishes from several Asian cuisines, among them those of
        Northern China, Mongolia, Hong Kong, Thailand and Japan.</string>
    <string name="sheyan_address">8 Ramban Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="sheyan_url">http://www.sheyan.rest-e.co.il/</string>
    <string name="sheyan_phone_number">+972539428640</string>

    <!-- Ricotta -->
    <string name="ricotta_name">Ricotta Restaurant</string>
    <string name="ricotta_summary">Italian style milky restaurant</string>
    <string name="ricotta_times">8am till the last diner</string>
    <string name="ricotta_description">Ricotta, a strictly kosher, Italian dairy restaurant is located in one of the most
        impressive buildings in Jerusalem\s high-tech district, at the entrance to Har Hotzvim, enjoying high quality atmosphere,
        a panoramic view and clear, mountain air.The restaurant\'s quiet location is perfect for intimate get-togethers far from the noise of the city.
    </string>
    <string name="ricotta_address">Science Park 3 Har Hotzvim</string>
    <string name="ricotta_url">http://www.ricotta.rest-e.co.il/</string>
    <string name="ricotta_number">+97253&#8211;8095155
</string>

    <!-- Waffle Bar -->
    <string name="waffle_name">Waffle Bar</string>
    <string name="waffle_summary">Great waffle, great times</string>
    <string name="waffle_times">8am until 11:30pm</string>
    <string name="waffle_description">Waffle Bar restaurant in Ramat Eshkol is located in the commercial center
        near the post office. It has a small indoor seating area and an enclosed seating space outdoors.
        In the good weather there is additional outdoor seating under umbrellas. </string>
    <string name="waffle_address">7 Paran Street Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="waffle_url"></string>
    <string name="waffle_phone_number">+9722&#8211;5815434</string>

    <!--Katzefet -->
    <string name="katzefet_name">Katzefet</string>
    <string name="katzefet_summary">Delicious Italian Ice Cream</string>
    <string name="katzefet_times"></string>
    <string name="katzefet_description">Katzefet Ice Cream is a Kosher Mehadrin yogurt and ice cream store with a huge selection of ice cream
        (including soft ice cream), bio yogurt, soft yogurt in four flavors, frozen yogurt, ice coffee, vanilla ice,
        passion fruit ice, French crepes, Belgian waffles, hot and cold drinks, fruit shakes, smoothies, milkshakes
        and ice cream cakes.The store offers free whipped cream and toppings.</string>
    <string name="katzefet_address">Rav-shefa Mall, Romema</string>
    <string name="katzefet_url">https://www.itraveljerusalem.com/rst/katzefet-ice-cream/</string>
    <string name="katzefet_phone_number">+9722&#8211;6253722</string>

</resources>
